Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: The Living Theatre
  - Strike for a Better Life - flyers, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - The Tablets- press release, reviews, flyers, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - The Tablets- script and adaptation, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Tax documents, 1973-1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Technical notes for props, equipment, stage, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Technical requirements for Antigone, Masse Mensch, The Archeology of Sleep, The Yellow Methuselah, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Telephone installations, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Telephone list, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Text permissions, 1982-1984 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - That Time- reviews, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Theandric Notebook- early draft, [1982] (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Theandric Notebook(copy), [1982] (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Theandric Notebook I(copy 2), [1982] (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Theandric Notebook II(copy 2), [1982] (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Theandric notes, [1984] (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - "Theatre and its Relevancy to the North and Latin American Realities", 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Theatre articles, 1964-1985 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Theatre notes, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Tonight We Improvise- program, Feb 1955, Mar 1955 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Tour - article, press release, schedule, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - "Travail Theatre" article, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - A Tribute to Julian Beck, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Jose Troya - resume, undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Tumult- flyer, undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Ubu the King and The Heroes- original ticket from the Cherry Lane Theatre, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Us poster by Julian Beck, undated (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Us- press, biographies, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Us- script by Karen Malpede, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Utopia, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Various items, 1955- (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Visa applications, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Visit to Julian Beck's grave site, August 16, 1989. (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Vktms- reviews, press releases, programs, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Vktms- script, undated (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Vktms- script, undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - War Resisters League, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Waste, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Samuel Waxman, MD, letter re. Julian Beck, April 15, 1985. (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - We Should … A Lie- press release, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - "Why Did You Do it, What Was it Like?", 1957 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - "Why Avant-Garde?" and "About Theatre Today" by Julian Beck, undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - William Carlos Williams letter, December 15, 1951. (photocopy) (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Win Magazine with Living Theatre article, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - "A Word Event in Memoriam Julian Beck", November 25, 1985. (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- Anne Masse, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- costume designs by Julian Beck (original drawings), 1982 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- France, Austria, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- script (photocopy), undated (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- script (photocopy with handwritten notes by Mark Amitin), 1982 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- French script (photocopy with notes by Tom Walker), undated (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- script for Joyce production, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - The Yellow Methuselah- technical requirements (Julian Beck handwritten MS), 1984 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - The Young Disciple- program, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - The Zero Method- press release, flyer, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 57)
- Series IV: World of Culture
  - Academy Players Directory, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040617600
  - Address list, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - AFTRA, 1978-1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Agencies, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - The Alchemical Theatre, 1986-1989 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Alien Comic (Tom Murrin), 1988 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Seth Allen, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - American College Theatre Festival, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - American College Theatre Festival, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - American Repertory Theatre, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Jo Andres, 1986- (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Jo Andres - Cindi Lauper video, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Jo Andres - Clemens Performing Arts Center residency, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Jo Andres - Eastern European tour, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Jo Andres press, 1984-1990 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Ann Arbor 8mm Film Festival, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Artservices Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - ATHE, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Atlanta Childrens' Theatre - travel, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Auditions, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Auditions, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Kirk Baily, 1988- (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Kirk Baily - Strange Turf, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Eszter Balint - Bail Jumper, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Stefan Balint - Day One, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - George Bartenieff, 1990- (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - George Bartenieff accounting, 1986- (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - George Bartenieff contracts, 1986-1993 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - George Bartenieff - Laser Man, Crime Story, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Bill Bastian, undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Isha Manna Beck, undated (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Isha Manna Beck - Law and Order, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Isha Manna Beck - The Roommates, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Julian Beck accounting, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Julian Beck - All My Children, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Julian Beck - costume and wardrobe info, undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Julian Beck - The Cotton Club, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Julian Beck - The Cotton Club reviews, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Julian Beck - Miami Vice, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Julian Beck - 9 1/2 Weeks, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Julian Beck - Playboy, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Julian Beck - Poltergeist II articles, reviews, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Julian Beck - Poltergeist II contact lists, correspondence, press, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Julian Beck - Poltergeist II press info, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Julian Beck - Poltergeist II script, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Julian Beck - Poltergeist II shooting schedule, agreement, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Julian Beck residual payments, 1985-1991 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618012
  - Julian Beck - The Two Jakes, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Tameron Beck, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Steven Ben Israel, 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Keith Berger, 1977- (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Keith Berger accounting, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Keith Berger correspondence, contracts, bookings, 1977-1988 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Keith Berger - The School of Charisma, Mar 1979 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Keith Berger and Sharon Diskin, 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Bonneau 1995 season (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Mark Boone Jr. accounting, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Mark Boone Jr. contracts, payments, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Mark Boone Jr. - Landlord Blues, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Mark Boone Jr. press, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Mark Boone Jr. resume, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre calendar, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Breakdown Services, 1985- (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Lee Breuer - As the World Turns, undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Lee Breuer - The Gospel at Colonus, 1984-1986 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Lee Breuer - Illinois State University, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Lee Breuer press, 1980-1987 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Lee Breuer resume, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Lee Breuer - Sister Suzie Cinema, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Lee Breuer travel, undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Brian Winthrop International: statements, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Brochure draft material, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music technical data, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Timothy Buckley, 1981-1986 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Michael Buscemi resume, undated (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Steve Buscemi accounting, 1986-1990 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Steve Buscemi - Animal Factory script, February 8, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Steve Buscemi - An Apartment Under the the Influence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Steve Buscemi - Bloodhounds of Broadway, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Steve Buscemi - Call Me, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Steve Buscemi correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Steve Buscemi - Deep Sleep, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Steve Buscemi - Heart, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Steve Buscemi - Heart press, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Steve Buscemi - Heart of Midnight, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Steve Buscemi - King of New York, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Steve Buscemi - Lonesome Dove, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Steve Buscemi - Miami Vice, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Steve Buscemi - Miller's Crossing, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Steve Buscemi - Mystery Train, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Steve Buscemi - New York Stories, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Steve Buscemi - Parting Glances, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Steve Buscemi press, 1987-1995 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Steve Buscemi - Reservoir Dogs, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Steve Buscemi resumes, biography, undated (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Steve Buscemi - Slaves of New York, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Steve Buscemi - The Street, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Steve Buscemi - Tales From the Dark Side, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Steve Buscemi - Trees Lounge, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Steve Buscemi - Trees Lounge screenplay, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - Steve Buscemi - Tuesday Night in Memphis, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Steve Buscemi - Twenty Bucks, undated (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Steve Buscemi various performances, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Steve Buscemi - Vibes, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Steve Buscemi - The Way it Is, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Steve Buscemi - William Tell, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 60)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr., 1984-1988 (Box 45, Folder 61)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. - Barkin' at the Moon, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618020
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. - Barkin' at the Moon screenplay Nov 12, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. - In Your Mind, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. press package, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. - St Marks, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. various, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Steve Buscemi and Mark Boone Jr. - Yap Thaw and Dead Reckoning, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - David Cale, 1987- (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - David Cale, 1987- (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - David Cale accounts 1, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - David Cale accounts 2, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - David Cale contracts, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - David Cale correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - David Cale flyers, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - David Cale - Four Faggots in Rich Sauce& other scripts, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - David Cale - Jacob's Pillow, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - David Cale - The Kitchen, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - David Cale - Moon Over Parador, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - David Cale - The Nature of Things, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - David Cale - Nexus Theatre layout, undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - David Cale press, 1986- (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - David Cale press, 1986- (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - David Cale - Random House, 1987-1989 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - David Cale - The Redthroats flyers, programs, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - David Cale - The Redthroats original light plot, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - David Cale - The Redthroats press, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - David Cale - The Redthroats script, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - David Cale - The Redthroats script, undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - David Cale - The Redthroats in Toronto, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - David Cale S.A.G. contract, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - David Cale - The Second Stage, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - David Cale - Smooch Music, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - David Cale - Smooch Music lighting design, undated (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - David Cale - Smooch Music script, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - David Cale - Smooch Music script, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - David Cale - Smooch Music sound equipment, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618038
  - David Cale - Sushi contract, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - David Cale - Teatro Vittoria, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - David Cale technical, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - David Cale touring info, contracts, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - David Cale transport, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Caravan Stage Company, 1976-1988 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Steven Cardoza, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Joseph Chaikin, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Joseph Chaikin, 1984-1992 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Joseph Chaikin - The Bald Soprano, Jun 1987 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Joseph Chaikin flyers, programs, 1982- (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Joseph Chaikin press, 1985-1992 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Joseph Chaikin - Struck Dumb, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Chaikin, Wayne Maugans - A Movie Star, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Chaikin, Sam Shepard - The War in Heaven, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Shami Chaikin, 1979-1990 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Shami Chaikin - Skip Tracer, Fake Book, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Shami Chaikin, Jean-Claude van Itallie - The Bag Lady, 1980-1985 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Shami Chaikin, Jean-Claude van Itallie - The Bag Lady press, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Shami Chaikin, Jean-Claude van Itallie - The Bag Lady script, undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Valerie Charles, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Valerie Charles accounting, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Valerie Charles press, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Valerie Charles scripts, undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Clients, undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Raphael Cohen, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - The Cotton Club(Beck and Malina), 1983 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Paula Court, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Cyberstorm, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Julia Dean, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Directors Forum, Jan 1989 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Directors' Workshop, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Joseph Di Rocco - Adam and the Experts, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - East of Eden West of Germany, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - East of Eden West of Germany casting, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - The Equalizer script and correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Peter Facinelli auditions, meetings, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Peter Facinelli contract with Mark Amitin, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Peter Facinelli contracts, correspondence, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Peter Facinelli - Foxfire, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Peter Facinelli - Honest call sheet, script, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Peter Facinelli - Honest script, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Peter Facinelli - Honest unit list, amended script, cast list, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Peter Facinelli - Kevin Spacey project script, undated (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Peter Facinelli - The Price of Love, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618046
  - Peter Facinelli - The Price of Love call sheets, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Peter Facinelli - The Price of Love Emmy campaign, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Peter Facinelli - The Price of Love script, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Peter Facinelli resume, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Peter Facinelli unidentified script, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Peter Facinelli - Vicious Circles script, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - George Ferencz, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - George Ferencz press, 1976-1987 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Crystal Field, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, programs, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Flyers, programs, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Flyers, programs, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Fourteen Karat Soul correspondence, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Fourteen Karat Soul press, 1980- (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Richard Ganoung, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Philip Glass in China, 1984-1986 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Spalding Gray - Almost You, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Spalding Gray press, 1984-1992 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Spalding Gray - Swimming to Cambodia, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Group 5, undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - William Gurr - All My Children, undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Joe Hackett - The Obscenity, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Joe Hackett resume, undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Peter Halacz - Fat Man and Little Boy, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Wilson Heredia, 1996- (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Wilson Heredia casting directors labels, undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Wilson Heredia casting meetings, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Wilson Heredia contracts, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Wilson Heredia - The New Americans, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Wilson Heredia press, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Wilson Heredia - Rent financial, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Wilson Heredia - Subway Stories, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Wilson Heredia, Jim Todd letter, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Hollywood Reporter ads for Steve Buscemi & Shirley Stoler, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Humana Festival, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Nathaniel Hunt, undated (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - In the Spirit, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - John Jesurun, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - John Kelly & Company, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Hans Kennon, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Kathy Kinney, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - The Kipper Kids, undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - The Kipper Kids contracts, correspondence, receipts, 1979-1988 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - The Kipper Kids: K.O. Kippers script breakdown, undated (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - The Kipper Kids at Lincoln Center, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - The Kipper Kids press, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618053
  - The Kipper Kids screenplay, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - The Kipper Kids technical, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - The Kipper Kids U.H.F., 1988 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - The Kitchen letter, November 25, 1987. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - La Gran Scena Opera, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - La Gran Scena Opera press, 1982- (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - La Mama e.t.c., 1984 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - La Mama technical specifications, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Maxine Lapiduss, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Maxine Lapiduss accounts, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Maxine Lapiduss press, 1985-1987 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Last Exit to Brooklyn, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Franne Lee - Agnes Smedley film, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Franne Lee - Appaloosa Rising, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Franne Lee - The Arbor, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Franne Lee artwork, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Franne Lee - Baby it's You work file, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Franne Lee - The Beard, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Franne Lee - Beauty and the Beast, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Franne Lee - biography, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Franne Lee - birthday party videos, [1985] (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Franne Lee - Blood Wedding script, rehearsal schedule, March 24, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Franne Lee, A Book on Design, undated (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Franne Lee - Bowling for Horror work file, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Franne Lee - Camelot, undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Franne Lee - Christmas Carols/ Butterfly Entertainment, undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Franne Lee - Live From Studio 811, Apr 20, 1981. (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Franne Lee - Love You to Death script, undated (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Franne Lee - Misplaced screenplay, March 27, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Franne Lee - City Kids screenplay, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618061
  - Franne Lee - Comedy Zone script, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Franne Lee - Comedy Zone work file, July 19, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Franne Lee - Come into My Parlor script, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Franne Lee - Come Up and See Me Sometime script, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Franne Lee correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Franne Lee costumes for unidentified productions, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Franne Lee - A Couple White Chicks Sitting Around Talking script, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Franne Lee - The Cure and other scripts, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Franne Lee - East Coast Arts, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Franne Lee - The Daffodil Ladies screenplay, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Franne Lee - Dead Ringer screenplay, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Franne Lee - Eating Raoul costumes, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Franne Lee - The Flight of the Dream Bird script, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Franne Lee - Getting a Job, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Franne Lee - The Goodman Theatre work file for Hotline, Jews, Gorilla, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Franne Lee - Home Free script, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Franne Lee - It Happens Everyday, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Franne Lee - Jack the Ripper script, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Franne Lee - The Little Prince script, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Franne Lee - The Little Rascals script, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Franne Lee - Live From Studio 8H, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Franne Lee - Mother Courage scripts, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Franne Lee - My Dinner with Andre script, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618079
  - Franne Lee notebook, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Franne Lee polaroids, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Franne Lee press, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Franne Lee recommendations, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Franne Lee - The Red Snake script, August 30, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Franne Lee resume, letters of application, 1985-1993 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Franne Lee - A Return to Salem's Lot screenplay, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Franne Lee - Rock & Roll work file, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Franne Lee - Seize the Day script, June 24, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Franne Lee - Shiva script, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Franne Lee - Slake's Limbo script, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Franne Lee - Square Pegs script, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Franne Lee - Star Child script, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Franne Lee - Street Heat script, notes, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Franne Lee - The Summer of Love - 1967, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Franne Lee - Suzanne Vega, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Franne Lee - Sweeney Todd script, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Franne Lee - Tails, You Lose screenplay, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Franne Lee - Trilogy of Involvements script, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Franne Lee - Twelve Dreams script, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Franne Lee - Uncle Tom's Cabin script, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Franne Lee unidentified script, undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Franne Lee unidentified script, undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Franne Lee unidentified script, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040618087
  - Franne Lee - Untitled Paul Simon Movie script, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Franne Lee - Wally Tonight proposal, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Franne Lee - When Girls Collide screenplay, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Franne Lee - The White Hotel script, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Franne Lee - Willie Stark screenplay, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Franne Lee - The Winter's Tale work file, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Mark Legan, 1982-1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Le Plan K international tour, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Lo st Paradise, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 10)